[
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which App you use to get snacks, drinks and cofee without cash in The Bridge?",
        "correct_answer": "Breasy",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Survivor.io",
            "Slack",
            "Bootstrap"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Frontend development, what is the most common and easily way to get fantasy in your web?",
        "correct_answer": "Bootstrap",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "React",
            "&#039;For&#039; loops",
            "Array.push()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What kind of loop is the first in the morning in the bridge??",
        "correct_answer": "Meet audio loop",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "do-While loop",
            "for loop",
            "Wubba Lubba dub loop"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "On Slack, who post more messages in #General?",
        "correct_answer": "Álvaro Fontán",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "David Garcia",
            "People who forgets stuff in class",
            "Alumns by mistake"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What Javascript Library let your computers fan look like it's going to take off?",
        "correct_answer": "React",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Alexandria Library",
            "Leaflet",
            "Node.js"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct way to turn on the microwave in the bridge?",
        "correct_answer": "Push the first button many times",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Push buttons randomly",
            "Wait for someone to finish and use the same",
            "Eat your cold meal"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What does '...' mean in Javascipt?",
        "correct_answer": "Spread and Rest operator",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "3 dots",
            "Dramatic Pause",
            "Etc"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How long it takes to complete our bootcamp?",
        "correct_answer": "16 weeks",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Almost a year",
            "15 days",
            "Just after learn React"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Is possible to open and close the Database conection in node.js?",
        "correct_answer": "Yes, we know how to do it",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "It's not necessary",
            "Is better only open the connection when server starts",
            "I'll try but i'll get errors"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What does MERN mean?",
        "correct_answer": "MongoDB, Express JS, React JS, Node JS",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Marquina Express LeaRN",
            "Muy Entretenido React: No",
            "Must Enhance Repository Native"
        ]
    }
]